{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954937451","data":{"timestamp":" 946954937451"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955004715","data":{"timestamp":" 946955004715"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955004763","data":{"timestamp":" 946955004762"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 9c44eb4f-c903-437e-8c1c-0f4428059ccc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955009996","data":{"timestamp":" 946955009996"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 9c44eb4f-c903-437e-8c1c-0f4428059ccc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2s.AV.mc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955015554","data":{"timestamp":" 946955015553"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 9c44eb4f-c903-437e-8c1c-0f4428059ccc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955020607","data":{"timestamp":" 946955020606"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 9c44eb4f-c903-437e-8c1c-0f4428059ccc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955032930","data":{"timestamp":" 946955032929"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955036978","data":{"timestamp":" 946955036978"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955038570","data":{"timestamp":" 946955038570"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955042290","data":{"timestamp":" 946955042290"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955043920","data":{"timestamp":" 946955043919"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955048552","data":{"timestamp":" 946955048552"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955050143","data":{"timestamp":" 946955050142"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955054480","data":{"timestamp":" 946955054480"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955056090","data":{"timestamp":" 946955056089"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955059934","data":{"timestamp":" 946955059933"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955061522","data":{"timestamp":" 946955061522"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955065552","data":{"timestamp":" 946955065552"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955067171","data":{"timestamp":" 946955067170"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955070743","data":{"timestamp":" 946955070743"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955072773","data":{"timestamp":" 946955072772"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955073029","data":{"timestamp":" 946955073029"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955107562","data":{"timestamp":" 946955107562"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 84457124-0472-46eb-9017-6d32df19a576"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955107636","data":{"timestamp":" 946955107636"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 2364b20a-0a95-4b76-b168-6cddd5ed06a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955115698","data":{"timestamp":" 946955115697"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 2364b20a-0a95-4b76-b168-6cddd5ed06a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956340419","data":{"timestamp":" 946956340419"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 2364b20a-0a95-4b76-b168-6cddd5ed06a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956352443","data":{"timestamp":" 946956352443"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-O-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956355770","data":{"timestamp":" 946956355770"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_N-O-Y"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956358995","data":{"timestamp":" 946956358995"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_L-O-M"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956362153","data":{"timestamp":" 946956362153"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_N-O-K"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956365116","data":{"timestamp":" 946956365116"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_F-O-V"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956369020","data":{"timestamp":" 946956369019"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_Z-J-O"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956372382","data":{"timestamp":" 946956372382"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_E-O-P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956375915","data":{"timestamp":" 946956375915"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-W-L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956379411","data":{"timestamp":" 946956379411"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_Y-K-O"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956382891","data":{"timestamp":" 946956382891"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-R-O"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956388656","data":{"timestamp":" 946956388655"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-R-O"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956420241","data":{"timestamp":" 946956420241"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 04860933-3a95-426f-96e6-4077721f5985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-R-O"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956420319","data":{"timestamp":" 946956420319"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a8e5015c-ce1c-43d8-8cdb-7c0623c5a766"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea ____________?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956430779","data":{"timestamp":" 946956430778"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-M-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956434891","data":{"timestamp":" 946956434891"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-M-U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956438414","data":{"timestamp":" 946956438414"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_Y-Z-O"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956441817","data":{"timestamp":" 946956441816"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-T-CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956445828","data":{"timestamp":" 946956445828"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_M-O-L"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956449079","data":{"timestamp":" 946956449079"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_L-O-A"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956453056","data":{"timestamp":" 946956453056"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-O-I"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956456604","data":{"timestamp":" 946956456603"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_K-N-O"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956459762","data":{"timestamp":" 946956459762"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-W-I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956463073","data":{"timestamp":" 946956463073"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_M-S-O"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956468838","data":{"timestamp":" 946956468834"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67096258-cc18-436c-91ac-0e355d0e37e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_O_M-S-O"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.rise.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956481693","data":{"timestamp":" 946956481693"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 9e8dcb7f-1d40-47f5-84bb-a9320cbf8a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.rise.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.rise.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956488390","data":{"timestamp":" 946956488390"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 9e8dcb7f-1d40-47f5-84bb-a9320cbf8a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.rise.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956500436","data":{"timestamp":" 946956500436"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 35f69520-914a-4cdd-b8cd-38a8e0c53da3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956506837","data":{"timestamp":" 946956506837"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 35f69520-914a-4cdd-b8cd-38a8e0c53da3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956506988","data":{"timestamp":" 946956506988"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 35f69520-914a-4cdd-b8cd-38a8e0c53da3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956619619","data":{"timestamp":" 946956619611"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 35f69520-914a-4cdd-b8cd-38a8e0c53da3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956619706","data":{"timestamp":" 946956619706"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 2b066b9e-a13b-4fa1-8100-9cda0f0852fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956644743","data":{"timestamp":" 946956644743"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956648226","data":{"timestamp":" 946956648226"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956651849","data":{"timestamp":" 946956651849"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956656574","data":{"timestamp":" 946956656574"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956661140","data":{"timestamp":" 946956661139"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956664966","data":{"timestamp":" 946956664966"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956669296","data":{"timestamp":" 946956669296"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956673088","data":{"timestamp":" 946956673088"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956676317","data":{"timestamp":" 946956676317"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956679729","data":{"timestamp":" 946956679729"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956683024","data":{"timestamp":" 946956683024"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956686115","data":{"timestamp":" 946956686115"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956692414","data":{"timestamp":" 946956692413"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956696114","data":{"timestamp":" 946956696114"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956699513","data":{"timestamp":" 946956699512"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956705220","data":{"timestamp":" 946956705219"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956710014","data":{"timestamp":" 946956710014"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956713731","data":{"timestamp":" 946956713731"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956718474","data":{"timestamp":" 946956718474"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956722091","data":{"timestamp":" 946956722091"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956726495","data":{"timestamp":" 946956726495"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956730248","data":{"timestamp":" 946956730248"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956734652","data":{"timestamp":" 946956734652"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956738100","data":{"timestamp":" 946956738100"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956745240","data":{"timestamp":" 946956745240"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956750156","data":{"timestamp":" 946956750156"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 64c90fb3-3276-458f-b1cf-f00e23e47fc7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956794493","data":{"timestamp":" 946956794493"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956822792","data":{"timestamp":" 946956822792"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956835174","data":{"timestamp":" 946956835173"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956848233","data":{"timestamp":" 946956848233"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956862151","data":{"timestamp":" 946956862151"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956893668","data":{"timestamp":" 946956893668"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956906839","data":{"timestamp":" 946956906839"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956920211","data":{"timestamp":" 946956920211"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956932947","data":{"timestamp":" 946956932947"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956943150","data":{"timestamp":" 946956943150"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956948710","data":{"timestamp":" 946956948710"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956957460","data":{"timestamp":" 946956957458"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8e44c9c0-ca5b-4532-ac9c-bcd0ef643af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956969110","data":{"timestamp":" 946956969110"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" bd2d1f15-a5ab-47ac-accc-56bf2abc7a9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956971280","data":{"timestamp":" 946956971279"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" bd2d1f15-a5ab-47ac-accc-56bf2abc7a9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956973490","data":{"timestamp":" 946956973490"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" bd2d1f15-a5ab-47ac-accc-56bf2abc7a9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956976741","data":{"timestamp":" 946956976741"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" bd2d1f15-a5ab-47ac-accc-56bf2abc7a9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956978177","data":{"timestamp":" 946956978177"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" bd2d1f15-a5ab-47ac-accc-56bf2abc7a9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956992295","data":{"timestamp":" 946956992295"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957001486","data":{"timestamp":" 946957001486"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957003058","data":{"timestamp":" 946957003058"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957009957","data":{"timestamp":" 946957009957"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957011565","data":{"timestamp":" 946957011564"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957016347","data":{"timestamp":" 946957016346"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957017978","data":{"timestamp":" 946957017978"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957021476","data":{"timestamp":" 946957021476"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957023085","data":{"timestamp":" 946957023084"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957025857","data":{"timestamp":" 946957025857"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957027449","data":{"timestamp":" 946957027449"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957029694","data":{"timestamp":" 946957029693"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957031300","data":{"timestamp":" 946957031299"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957037375","data":{"timestamp":" 946957037374"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957039027","data":{"timestamp":" 946957039026"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957041369","data":{"timestamp":" 946957041369"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957042945","data":{"timestamp":" 946957042945"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957046939","data":{"timestamp":" 946957046938"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957048552","data":{"timestamp":" 946957048552"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957051582","data":{"timestamp":" 946957051582"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957053244","data":{"timestamp":" 946957053243"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957055750","data":{"timestamp":" 946957055750"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957055939","data":{"timestamp":" 946957055939"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 4a2abff4-3f7e-41c5-842f-3de47d079bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957067860","data":{"timestamp":" 946957067859"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957077653","data":{"timestamp":" 946957077653"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957079233","data":{"timestamp":" 946957079233"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957085779","data":{"timestamp":" 946957085779"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957087397","data":{"timestamp":" 946957087396"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957089760","data":{"timestamp":" 946957089759"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957091355","data":{"timestamp":" 946957091355"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957095863","data":{"timestamp":" 946957095863"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957097526","data":{"timestamp":" 946957097526"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957099988","data":{"timestamp":" 946957099988"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957101561","data":{"timestamp":" 946957101561"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957104589","data":{"timestamp":" 946957104588"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957106256","data":{"timestamp":" 946957106255"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957109388","data":{"timestamp":" 946957109388"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957111001","data":{"timestamp":" 946957111000"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957114308","data":{"timestamp":" 946957114308"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957115875","data":{"timestamp":" 946957115875"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957120777","data":{"timestamp":" 946957120777"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957122383","data":{"timestamp":" 946957122383"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957125601","data":{"timestamp":" 946957125601"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957127155","data":{"timestamp":" 946957127155"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957132132","data":{"timestamp":" 946957132132"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957133732","data":{"timestamp":" 946957133731"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957136263","data":{"timestamp":" 946957136262"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957137873","data":{"timestamp":" 946957137872"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957140212","data":{"timestamp":" 946957140211"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957142235","data":{"timestamp":" 946957142233"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957142363","data":{"timestamp":" 946957142363"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" a35e1163-4b8d-4d17-bdb2-0146671726a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957153044","data":{"timestamp":" 946957153043"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957154225","data":{"timestamp":" 946957154222"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957155127","data":{"timestamp":" 946957155126"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957156219","data":{"timestamp":" 946957156218"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957157245","data":{"timestamp":" 946957157244"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957158113","data":{"timestamp":" 946957158112"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957159230","data":{"timestamp":" 946957159229"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957159901","data":{"timestamp":" 946957159900"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957161203","data":{"timestamp":" 946957161201"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957163738","data":{"timestamp":" 946957163738"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957163932","data":{"timestamp":" 946957163931"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957164908","data":{"timestamp":" 946957164908"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957166287","data":{"timestamp":" 946957166287"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957166431","data":{"timestamp":" 946957166431"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957167576","data":{"timestamp":" 946957167576"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957168221","data":{"timestamp":" 946957168221"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957169317","data":{"timestamp":" 946957169316"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957170118","data":{"timestamp":" 946957170117"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957170239","data":{"timestamp":" 946957170238"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957170942","data":{"timestamp":" 946957170942"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957173990","data":{"timestamp":" 946957173989"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957174868","data":{"timestamp":" 946957174867"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957175104","data":{"timestamp":" 946957175103"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957175745","data":{"timestamp":" 946957175745"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957175865","data":{"timestamp":" 946957175865"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957176874","data":{"timestamp":" 946957176873"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957177781","data":{"timestamp":" 946957177781"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957178467","data":{"timestamp":" 946957178467"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957179752","data":{"timestamp":" 946957179752"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957182315","data":{"timestamp":" 946957182315"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957183359","data":{"timestamp":" 946957183358"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957183560","data":{"timestamp":" 946957183560"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957184296","data":{"timestamp":" 946957184296"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957185306","data":{"timestamp":" 946957185304"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" MINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957186307","data":{"timestamp":" 946957186304"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957187055","data":{"timestamp":" 946957187055"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957187657","data":{"timestamp":" 946957187657"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957188516","data":{"timestamp":" 946957188516"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957189033","data":{"timestamp":" 946957189033"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957189880","data":{"timestamp":" 946957189880"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957193254","data":{"timestamp":" 946957193254"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957193940","data":{"timestamp":" 946957193939"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957194746","data":{"timestamp":" 946957194746"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957195882","data":{"timestamp":" 946957195882"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957196538","data":{"timestamp":" 946957196538"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957197195","data":{"timestamp":" 946957197191"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957197888","data":{"timestamp":" 946957197888"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957198820","data":{"timestamp":" 946957198819"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957199713","data":{"timestamp":" 946957199713"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957199952","data":{"timestamp":" 946957199952"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957201250","data":{"timestamp":" 946957201249"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ILIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957201848","data":{"timestamp":" 946957201848"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957204452","data":{"timestamp":" 946957204452"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957204794","data":{"timestamp":" 946957204794"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957205544","data":{"timestamp":" 946957205544"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957207187","data":{"timestamp":" 946957207187"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957207662","data":{"timestamp":" 946957207661"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957208166","data":{"timestamp":" 946957208166"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957208658","data":{"timestamp":" 946957208657"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957211871","data":{"timestamp":" 946957211871"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957212546","data":{"timestamp":" 946957212546"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957214010","data":{"timestamp":" 946957214010"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957214622","data":{"timestamp":" 946957214622"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957215219","data":{"timestamp":" 946957215219"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957215917","data":{"timestamp":" 946957215917"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957216340","data":{"timestamp":" 946957216340"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957217344","data":{"timestamp":" 946957217344"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957220378","data":{"timestamp":" 946957220378"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957221372","data":{"timestamp":" 946957221371"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957222377","data":{"timestamp":" 946957222377"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957222899","data":{"timestamp":" 946957222899"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957223081","data":{"timestamp":" 946957223081"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957224322","data":{"timestamp":" 946957224322"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957225728","data":{"timestamp":" 946957225728"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957225978","data":{"timestamp":" 946957225977"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957227116","data":{"timestamp":" 946957227116"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957227697","data":{"timestamp":" 946957227696"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957230754","data":{"timestamp":" 946957230754"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957231722","data":{"timestamp":" 946957231721"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957232455","data":{"timestamp":" 946957232455"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957233357","data":{"timestamp":" 946957233356"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957236442","data":{"timestamp":" 946957236441"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957237207","data":{"timestamp":" 946957237207"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957237916","data":{"timestamp":" 946957237916"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957238641","data":{"timestamp":" 946957238641"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957238891","data":{"timestamp":" 946957238890"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957239633","data":{"timestamp":" 946957239631"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957241033","data":{"timestamp":" 946957241032"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957244328","data":{"timestamp":" 946957244328"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957245113","data":{"timestamp":" 946957245113"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957245877","data":{"timestamp":" 946957245876"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957246064","data":{"timestamp":" 946957246064"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957247077","data":{"timestamp":" 946957247077"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957247900","data":{"timestamp":" 946957247900"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957250359","data":{"timestamp":" 946957250358"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957250612","data":{"timestamp":" 946957250612"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957251284","data":{"timestamp":" 946957251284"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957252370","data":{"timestamp":" 946957252369"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957253401","data":{"timestamp":" 946957253400"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" KUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957253936","data":{"timestamp":" 946957253936"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957254623","data":{"timestamp":" 946957254623"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957254818","data":{"timestamp":" 946957254818"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957255525","data":{"timestamp":" 946957255525"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957255731","data":{"timestamp":" 946957255731"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957256636","data":{"timestamp":" 946957256635"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957259452","data":{"timestamp":" 946957259451"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957260071","data":{"timestamp":" 946957260071"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957260938","data":{"timestamp":" 946957260938"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957261743","data":{"timestamp":" 946957261743"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957261962","data":{"timestamp":" 946957261962"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957262626","data":{"timestamp":" 946957262626"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAHATI"," userResponse":" BAHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957263065","data":{"timestamp":" 946957263064"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957266127","data":{"timestamp":" 946957266126"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957266951","data":{"timestamp":" 946957266949"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957267461","data":{"timestamp":" 946957267461"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957267727","data":{"timestamp":" 946957267726"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957268453","data":{"timestamp":" 946957268453"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957268692","data":{"timestamp":" 946957268692"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957269891","data":{"timestamp":" 946957269890"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957270691","data":{"timestamp":" 946957270691"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957271560","data":{"timestamp":" 946957271560"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957272064","data":{"timestamp":" 946957272063"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957275340","data":{"timestamp":" 946957275339"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOTELEA"," userResponse":" ALIPOTELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957276542","data":{"timestamp":" 946957276541"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957279042","data":{"timestamp":" 946957279042"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957280595","data":{"timestamp":" 946957280595"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957284069","data":{"timestamp":" 946957284069"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" ALIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957284646","data":{"timestamp":" 946957284645"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957284771","data":{"timestamp":" 946957284771"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957285216","data":{"timestamp":" 946957285216"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957285459","data":{"timestamp":" 946957285458"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957286193","data":{"timestamp":" 946957286192"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EDOME"," userResponse":" EDOME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957287523","data":{"timestamp":" 946957287523"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" KUSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957288690","data":{"timestamp":" 946957288690"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957291124","data":{"timestamp":" 946957291124"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957291773","data":{"timestamp":" 946957291773"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957292808","data":{"timestamp":" 946957292808"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957293997","data":{"timestamp":" 946957293996"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957294233","data":{"timestamp":" 946957294233"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957295027","data":{"timestamp":" 946957295026"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOTA"," userResponse":" KUOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957295661","data":{"timestamp":" 946957295660"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957298673","data":{"timestamp":" 946957298673"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957299211","data":{"timestamp":" 946957299210"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957299856","data":{"timestamp":" 946957299856"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957300962","data":{"timestamp":" 946957300962"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957302359","data":{"timestamp":" 946957302359"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957303255","data":{"timestamp":" 946957303255"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957303746","data":{"timestamp":" 946957303746"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957304373","data":{"timestamp":" 946957304373"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957304834","data":{"timestamp":" 946957304834"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957305679","data":{"timestamp":" 946957305679"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957308357","data":{"timestamp":" 946957308357"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957309818","data":{"timestamp":" 946957309818"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFANANA"," userResponse":" ALIYEFANANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957310018","data":{"timestamp":" 946957310018"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957311229","data":{"timestamp":" 946957311229"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957312201","data":{"timestamp":" 946957312200"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957313432","data":{"timestamp":" 946957313432"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNGA"," userResponse":" AKIMCHUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957316338","data":{"timestamp":" 946957316338"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957317033","data":{"timestamp":" 946957317033"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957318734","data":{"timestamp":" 946957318733"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITABASAMU"," userResponse":" ALITABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957319351","data":{"timestamp":" 946957319350"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957319974","data":{"timestamp":" 946957319974"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957320711","data":{"timestamp":" 946957320711"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957321763","data":{"timestamp":" 946957321762"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957322039","data":{"timestamp":" 946957322039"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957322745","data":{"timestamp":" 946957322744"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957322941","data":{"timestamp":" 946957322940"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957323650","data":{"timestamp":" 946957323648"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957326019","data":{"timestamp":" 946957326018"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957327669","data":{"timestamp":" 946957327669"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," userResponse":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957328420","data":{"timestamp":" 946957328419"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957328829","data":{"timestamp":" 946957328829"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957329701","data":{"timestamp":" 946957329700"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" KUCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957330483","data":{"timestamp":" 946957330481"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957331162","data":{"timestamp":" 946957331161"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957332535","data":{"timestamp":" 946957332535"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957335480","data":{"timestamp":" 946957335479"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957336864","data":{"timestamp":" 946957336864"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957337389","data":{"timestamp":" 946957337388"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957337937","data":{"timestamp":" 946957337937"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957338538","data":{"timestamp":" 946957338537"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957338747","data":{"timestamp":" 946957338747"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 07e10bcb-9dcc-48ff-b54a-5c23cdbdf75d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957526763","data":{"timestamp":" 946957526763"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957527772","data":{"timestamp":" 946957527772"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957527965","data":{"timestamp":" 946957527965"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957528612","data":{"timestamp":" 946957528612"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957529190","data":{"timestamp":" 946957529190"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957529672","data":{"timestamp":" 946957529672"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957530099","data":{"timestamp":" 946957530098"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957530543","data":{"timestamp":" 946957530543"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957530718","data":{"timestamp":" 946957530718"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957531317","data":{"timestamp":" 946957531316"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957531799","data":{"timestamp":" 946957531799"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957534493","data":{"timestamp":" 946957534492"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957535075","data":{"timestamp":" 946957535074"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957535615","data":{"timestamp":" 946957535615"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957535837","data":{"timestamp":" 946957535837"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957536232","data":{"timestamp":" 946957536232"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957537034","data":{"timestamp":" 946957537032"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957539275","data":{"timestamp":" 946957539274"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957539718","data":{"timestamp":" 946957539718"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957539912","data":{"timestamp":" 946957539912"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957540657","data":{"timestamp":" 946957540657"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957541501","data":{"timestamp":" 946957541501"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957541955","data":{"timestamp":" 946957541955"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957542119","data":{"timestamp":" 946957542119"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957542733","data":{"timestamp":" 946957542733"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFU"," userResponse":" SAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957542848","data":{"timestamp":" 946957542848"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957543372","data":{"timestamp":" 946957543372"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957544753","data":{"timestamp":" 946957544753"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957548007","data":{"timestamp":" 946957548007"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957548879","data":{"timestamp":" 946957548878"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957549121","data":{"timestamp":" 946957549120"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957549613","data":{"timestamp":" 946957549613"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957549777","data":{"timestamp":" 946957549777"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957550334","data":{"timestamp":" 946957550333"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957551103","data":{"timestamp":" 946957551102"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITATU"," userResponse":" MITATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957552524","data":{"timestamp":" 946957552524"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957553029","data":{"timestamp":" 946957553029"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957554041","data":{"timestamp":" 946957554040"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEZA"," userResponse":" KUPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957554632","data":{"timestamp":" 946957554632"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWEZO"," userResponse":" UWEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957554810","data":{"timestamp":" 946957554809"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957555474","data":{"timestamp":" 946957555473"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957558074","data":{"timestamp":" 946957558074"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957558672","data":{"timestamp":" 946957558671"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957559475","data":{"timestamp":" 946957559475"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957560125","data":{"timestamp":" 946957560125"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957560598","data":{"timestamp":" 946957560598"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957561517","data":{"timestamp":" 946957561516"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TALANTA"," userResponse":" TALANTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957564815","data":{"timestamp":" 946957564815"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957565663","data":{"timestamp":" 946957565663"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITENDA"," userResponse":" ALITENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957566136","data":{"timestamp":" 946957566135"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957567083","data":{"timestamp":" 946957567081"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957567923","data":{"timestamp":" 946957567922"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957568683","data":{"timestamp":" 946957568682"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957569235","data":{"timestamp":" 946957569234"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957569466","data":{"timestamp":" 946957569466"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957569852","data":{"timestamp":" 946957569851"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957570396","data":{"timestamp":" 946957570396"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957571590","data":{"timestamp":" 946957571590"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957572274","data":{"timestamp":" 946957572274"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957574270","data":{"timestamp":" 946957574270"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957575040","data":{"timestamp":" 946957575040"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFANO"," userResponse":" MFANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957576011","data":{"timestamp":" 946957576010"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957576650","data":{"timestamp":" 946957576649"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKETI"," userResponse":" KUKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957576825","data":{"timestamp":" 946957576824"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957577213","data":{"timestamp":" 946957577213"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957577853","data":{"timestamp":" 946957577852"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957578345","data":{"timestamp":" 946957578344"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957579180","data":{"timestamp":" 946957579180"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJADILI"," userResponse":" KUJADILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957579627","data":{"timestamp":" 946957579626"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957580252","data":{"timestamp":" 946957580252"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHIMU"," userResponse":" MUHIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957583115","data":{"timestamp":" 946957583115"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957583319","data":{"timestamp":" 946957583319"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957583911","data":{"timestamp":" 946957583910"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957584754","data":{"timestamp":" 946957584754"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957585384","data":{"timestamp":" 946957585384"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957586130","data":{"timestamp":" 946957586129"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957586526","data":{"timestamp":" 946957586526"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957586713","data":{"timestamp":" 946957586713"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957587096","data":{"timestamp":" 946957587096"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957587865","data":{"timestamp":" 946957587865"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957590814","data":{"timestamp":" 946957590813"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" WALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957591691","data":{"timestamp":" 946957591691"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957592433","data":{"timestamp":" 946957592432"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957592677","data":{"timestamp":" 946957592677"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957593374","data":{"timestamp":" 946957593373"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957593853","data":{"timestamp":" 946957593853"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957594506","data":{"timestamp":" 946957594504"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957595202","data":{"timestamp":" 946957595202"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957597789","data":{"timestamp":" 946957597789"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957598569","data":{"timestamp":" 946957598565"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957598767","data":{"timestamp":" 946957598766"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957599146","data":{"timestamp":" 946957599146"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957599584","data":{"timestamp":" 946957599584"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957600084","data":{"timestamp":" 946957600083"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957603167","data":{"timestamp":" 946957603167"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957604091","data":{"timestamp":" 946957604091"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957604858","data":{"timestamp":" 946957604858"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957605687","data":{"timestamp":" 946957605687"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957606344","data":{"timestamp":" 946957606343"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957608812","data":{"timestamp":" 946957608811"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957609425","data":{"timestamp":" 946957609425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957610377","data":{"timestamp":" 946957610377"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957611412","data":{"timestamp":" 946957611411"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957612585","data":{"timestamp":" 946957612584"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957613899","data":{"timestamp":" 946957613899"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" UNAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957614260","data":{"timestamp":" 946957614260"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957614804","data":{"timestamp":" 946957614804"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957615327","data":{"timestamp":" 946957615327"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957616247","data":{"timestamp":" 946957616247"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957619379","data":{"timestamp":" 946957619378"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957620652","data":{"timestamp":" 946957620652"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957621466","data":{"timestamp":" 946957621466"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAKUJA"," userResponse":" ZINAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957621756","data":{"timestamp":" 946957621756"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957622541","data":{"timestamp":" 946957622541"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957625408","data":{"timestamp":" 946957625408"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZISIKIA"," userResponse":" NAZISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957626105","data":{"timestamp":" 946957626105"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWANI"," userResponse":" KICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957626738","data":{"timestamp":" 946957626738"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957627372","data":{"timestamp":" 946957627372"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957628414","data":{"timestamp":" 946957628413"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZIIMBA"," userResponse":" NAZIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957631751","data":{"timestamp":" 946957631751"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957632797","data":{"timestamp":" 946957632797"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957633714","data":{"timestamp":" 946957633714"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957634254","data":{"timestamp":" 946957634254"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957635000","data":{"timestamp":" 946957634999"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957635934","data":{"timestamp":" 946957635933"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957636833","data":{"timestamp":" 946957636832"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOHISI"," userResponse":" ALIPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957637378","data":{"timestamp":" 946957637378"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957640040","data":{"timestamp":" 946957640039"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957641345","data":{"timestamp":" 946957641345"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957642312","data":{"timestamp":" 946957642311"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957643284","data":{"timestamp":" 946957643284"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957644577","data":{"timestamp":" 946957644577"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957645310","data":{"timestamp":" 946957645310"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957647856","data":{"timestamp":" 946957647856"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957648717","data":{"timestamp":" 946957648716"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957649800","data":{"timestamp":" 946957649799"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUATIA"," userResponse":" KUFUATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957650119","data":{"timestamp":" 946957650119"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957650689","data":{"timestamp":" 946957650689"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957651170","data":{"timestamp":" 946957651170"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957652106","data":{"timestamp":" 946957652106"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957655279","data":{"timestamp":" 946957655279"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957655831","data":{"timestamp":" 946957655830"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957656305","data":{"timestamp":" 946957656304"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957656473","data":{"timestamp":" 946957656473"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957657251","data":{"timestamp":" 946957657250"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957658240","data":{"timestamp":" 946957658240"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957658999","data":{"timestamp":" 946957658998"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957659591","data":{"timestamp":" 946957659590"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957660415","data":{"timestamp":" 946957660415"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ANGEMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957662821","data":{"timestamp":" 946957662820"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957663933","data":{"timestamp":" 946957663933"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUBALI"," userResponse":" ANGEKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957664512","data":{"timestamp":" 946957664511"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957665225","data":{"timestamp":" 946957665224"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957665733","data":{"timestamp":" 946957665732"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957666474","data":{"timestamp":" 946957666474"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957669359","data":{"timestamp":" 946957669359"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957670060","data":{"timestamp":" 946957670060"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957670810","data":{"timestamp":" 946957670810"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957671172","data":{"timestamp":" 946957671172"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957671977","data":{"timestamp":" 946957671977"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" WALIPORUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957672805","data":{"timestamp":" 946957672805"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957673960","data":{"timestamp":" 946957673960"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957674762","data":{"timestamp":" 946957674761"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957675314","data":{"timestamp":" 946957675314"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957678007","data":{"timestamp":" 946957678007"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957678706","data":{"timestamp":" 946957678705"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957679318","data":{"timestamp":" 946957679317"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957680102","data":{"timestamp":" 946957680102"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957680796","data":{"timestamp":" 946957680796"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957680986","data":{"timestamp":" 946957680986"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957681434","data":{"timestamp":" 946957681434"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957681945","data":{"timestamp":" 946957681945"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957684644","data":{"timestamp":" 946957684644"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957685016","data":{"timestamp":" 946957685016"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957685838","data":{"timestamp":" 946957685838"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957686660","data":{"timestamp":" 946957686659"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957687440","data":{"timestamp":" 946957687439"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957689999","data":{"timestamp":" 946957689998"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957690816","data":{"timestamp":" 946957690815"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957693386","data":{"timestamp":" 946957693386"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957694240","data":{"timestamp":" 946957694240"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957694842","data":{"timestamp":" 946957694841"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957695534","data":{"timestamp":" 946957695533"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957695695","data":{"timestamp":" 946957695695"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957696047","data":{"timestamp":" 946957696047"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957696858","data":{"timestamp":" 946957696858"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957697659","data":{"timestamp":" 946957697659"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957698530","data":{"timestamp":" 946957698530"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" AMEPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957701112","data":{"timestamp":" 946957701112"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957701770","data":{"timestamp":" 946957701770"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957702284","data":{"timestamp":" 946957702283"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957703683","data":{"timestamp":" 946957703682"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957704260","data":{"timestamp":" 946957704259"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957704884","data":{"timestamp":" 946957704883"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957705265","data":{"timestamp":" 946957705265"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957706136","data":{"timestamp":" 946957706135"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPWEKE"," userResponse":" UPWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957706967","data":{"timestamp":" 946957706967"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957710132","data":{"timestamp":" 946957710130"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957711317","data":{"timestamp":" 946957711317"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957713792","data":{"timestamp":" 946957713791"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957714764","data":{"timestamp":" 946957714763"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ATAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957715391","data":{"timestamp":" 946957715390"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957716263","data":{"timestamp":" 946957716263"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957717096","data":{"timestamp":" 946957717096"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957717620","data":{"timestamp":" 946957717620"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957718106","data":{"timestamp":" 946957718105"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957720931","data":{"timestamp":" 946957720930"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957721456","data":{"timestamp":" 946957721456"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957721975","data":{"timestamp":" 946957721975"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957723120","data":{"timestamp":" 946957723120"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIDHARAU"," userResponse":" WALIDHARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957723671","data":{"timestamp":" 946957723670"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957724135","data":{"timestamp":" 946957724135"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957726641","data":{"timestamp":" 946957726641"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957726859","data":{"timestamp":" 946957726859"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957728050","data":{"timestamp":" 946957728049"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957730459","data":{"timestamp":" 946957730458"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957730650","data":{"timestamp":" 946957730650"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957731371","data":{"timestamp":" 946957731371"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957732455","data":{"timestamp":" 946957732454"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYEONA"," userResponse":" ASIYEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957735330","data":{"timestamp":" 946957735329"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNADHANI"," userResponse":" UNADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957735740","data":{"timestamp":" 946957735740"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957736081","data":{"timestamp":" 946957736081"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957737114","data":{"timestamp":" 946957737114"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAMSAIDIA"," userResponse":" UTAMSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957740092","data":{"timestamp":" 946957740092"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957740731","data":{"timestamp":" 946957740730"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957741444","data":{"timestamp":" 946957741444"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957742258","data":{"timestamp":" 946957742258"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUKATA"," userResponse":" HAKUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957742810","data":{"timestamp":" 946957742810"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957745020","data":{"timestamp":" 946957745020"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957745400","data":{"timestamp":" 946957745400"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957745801","data":{"timestamp":" 946957745801"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957746325","data":{"timestamp":" 946957746325"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957746716","data":{"timestamp":" 946957746716"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957747198","data":{"timestamp":" 946957747197"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957748206","data":{"timestamp":" 946957748205"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957748814","data":{"timestamp":" 946957748814"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOYO"," userResponse":" MOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957751463","data":{"timestamp":" 946957751462"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957752452","data":{"timestamp":" 946957752452"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957752611","data":{"timestamp":" 946957752610"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957753428","data":{"timestamp":" 946957753428"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957754652","data":{"timestamp":" 946957754652"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNITULIZA"," userResponse":" HUNITULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957755099","data":{"timestamp":" 946957755099"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957755624","data":{"timestamp":" 946957755624"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957755827","data":{"timestamp":" 946957755826"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957756361","data":{"timestamp":" 946957756361"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957759792","data":{"timestamp":" 946957759791"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAMTULIZA"," userResponse":" ZITAMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957760759","data":{"timestamp":" 946957760759"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957760992","data":{"timestamp":" 946957760991"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957761236","data":{"timestamp":" 946957761236"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957764669","data":{"timestamp":" 946957764668"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957765737","data":{"timestamp":" 946957765736"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957766673","data":{"timestamp":" 946957766672"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957767646","data":{"timestamp":" 946957767646"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957768046","data":{"timestamp":" 946957768045"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957768601","data":{"timestamp":" 946957768601"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957770076","data":{"timestamp":" 946957770075"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMWELEKEZE"," userResponse":" AMWELEKEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957770746","data":{"timestamp":" 946957770745"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957771149","data":{"timestamp":" 946957771149"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957771543","data":{"timestamp":" 946957771542"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957771746","data":{"timestamp":" 946957771745"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957772142","data":{"timestamp":" 946957772141"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957772873","data":{"timestamp":" 946957772873"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957776242","data":{"timestamp":" 946957776242"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957776828","data":{"timestamp":" 946957776828"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957776923","data":{"timestamp":" 946957776922"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957777539","data":{"timestamp":" 946957777539"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957778093","data":{"timestamp":" 946957778093"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957778605","data":{"timestamp":" 946957778604"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957779240","data":{"timestamp":" 946957779239"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957779850","data":{"timestamp":" 946957779850"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957780318","data":{"timestamp":" 946957780318"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957780936","data":{"timestamp":" 946957780936"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957782009","data":{"timestamp":" 946957782009"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957784308","data":{"timestamp":" 946957784307"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957784982","data":{"timestamp":" 946957784981"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957785866","data":{"timestamp":" 946957785865"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957786137","data":{"timestamp":" 946957786136"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957786615","data":{"timestamp":" 946957786615"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957787459","data":{"timestamp":" 946957787459"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957788403","data":{"timestamp":" 946957788402"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIANZA"," userResponse":" KILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957789426","data":{"timestamp":" 946957789425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957790109","data":{"timestamp":" 946957790109"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957790762","data":{"timestamp":" 946957790762"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957793790","data":{"timestamp":" 946957793790"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAFANYI"," userResponse":" WAFANYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957794330","data":{"timestamp":" 946957794330"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957795070","data":{"timestamp":" 946957795067"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957796082","data":{"timestamp":" 946957796082"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957796628","data":{"timestamp":" 946957796628"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957797247","data":{"timestamp":" 946957797247"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957798217","data":{"timestamp":" 946957798217"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIZOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957799051","data":{"timestamp":" 946957799050"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957802538","data":{"timestamp":" 946957802537"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKILIZA"," userResponse":" WALISIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957803147","data":{"timestamp":" 946957803146"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957804178","data":{"timestamp":" 946957804178"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTAMU"," userResponse":" MTAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957804327","data":{"timestamp":" 946957804327"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957805035","data":{"timestamp":" 946957805034"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957807498","data":{"timestamp":" 946957807498"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957808209","data":{"timestamp":" 946957808209"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957809074","data":{"timestamp":" 946957809074"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957809639","data":{"timestamp":" 946957809639"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957810393","data":{"timestamp":" 946957810393"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957811702","data":{"timestamp":" 946957811702"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957812729","data":{"timestamp":" 946957812728"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFAULU"," userResponse":" ALIYEFAULU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957813493","data":{"timestamp":" 946957813493"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957813967","data":{"timestamp":" 946957813967"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957816526","data":{"timestamp":" 946957816525"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957817190","data":{"timestamp":" 946957817190"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957817695","data":{"timestamp":" 946957817695"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957818563","data":{"timestamp":" 946957818562"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYEONA"," userResponse":" ASIYEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957819427","data":{"timestamp":" 946957819427"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAWEZA"," userResponse":" ATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957820580","data":{"timestamp":" 946957820579"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957823777","data":{"timestamp":" 946957823777"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957824835","data":{"timestamp":" 946957824835"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKAMILISHA"," userResponse":" ALIKAMILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957825383","data":{"timestamp":" 946957825379"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957825729","data":{"timestamp":" 946957825729"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957826302","data":{"timestamp":" 946957826302"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957827387","data":{"timestamp":" 946957827387"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957828174","data":{"timestamp":" 946957828173"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957831212","data":{"timestamp":" 946957831211"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957831474","data":{"timestamp":" 946957831474"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957832141","data":{"timestamp":" 946957832141"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957832760","data":{"timestamp":" 946957832759"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKA"," userResponse":" ALITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957833114","data":{"timestamp":" 946957833114"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957833577","data":{"timestamp":" 946957833577"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957834222","data":{"timestamp":" 946957834222"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957834380","data":{"timestamp":" 946957834379"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957834973","data":{"timestamp":" 946957834973"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957836611","data":{"timestamp":" 946957836607"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957837428","data":{"timestamp":" 946957837428"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957838139","data":{"timestamp":" 946957838138"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957841121","data":{"timestamp":" 946957841121"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957841364","data":{"timestamp":" 946957841364"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957841753","data":{"timestamp":" 946957841753"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957842922","data":{"timestamp":" 946957842922"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957843455","data":{"timestamp":" 946957843454"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957844189","data":{"timestamp":" 946957844189"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUJA"," userResponse":" WALIKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957844743","data":{"timestamp":" 946957844743"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957845587","data":{"timestamp":" 946957845587"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEMBEBA"," userResponse":" WAMEMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957846062","data":{"timestamp":" 946957846061"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957846831","data":{"timestamp":" 946957846830"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957847489","data":{"timestamp":" 946957847488"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHELA"," userResponse":" MACHELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957850286","data":{"timestamp":" 946957850286"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMKUTA"," userResponse":" WALIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957850779","data":{"timestamp":" 946957850778"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957850955","data":{"timestamp":" 946957850955"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957851659","data":{"timestamp":" 946957851659"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957852273","data":{"timestamp":" 946957852273"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957853720","data":{"timestamp":" 946957853720"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHAPWA"," userResponse":" AMECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957854176","data":{"timestamp":" 946957854176"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957854825","data":{"timestamp":" 946957854825"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUACHWA"," userResponse":" KUACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957855288","data":{"timestamp":" 946957855288"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957855506","data":{"timestamp":" 946957855506"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957856090","data":{"timestamp":" 946957856089"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957859062","data":{"timestamp":" 946957859062"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957859758","data":{"timestamp":" 946957859758"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957861105","data":{"timestamp":" 946957861104"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957861877","data":{"timestamp":" 946957861876"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957863175","data":{"timestamp":" 946957863175"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957863544","data":{"timestamp":" 946957863544"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957863976","data":{"timestamp":" 946957863975"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957864608","data":{"timestamp":" 946957864607"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957867861","data":{"timestamp":" 946957867860"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMZAWADI"," userResponse":" ALIMZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957868818","data":{"timestamp":" 946957868818"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957869242","data":{"timestamp":" 946957869241"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957870232","data":{"timestamp":" 946957870231"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLIWAZA"," userResponse":" KUMLIWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957873522","data":{"timestamp":" 946957873522"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957874540","data":{"timestamp":" 946957874540"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957874790","data":{"timestamp":" 946957874790"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957875427","data":{"timestamp":" 946957875426"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957876443","data":{"timestamp":" 946957876442"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957877161","data":{"timestamp":" 946957877161"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957877772","data":{"timestamp":" 946957877771"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957878486","data":{"timestamp":" 946957878485"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957879552","data":{"timestamp":" 946957879552"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAIDIWA"," userResponse":" KUSAIDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957880412","data":{"timestamp":" 946957880411"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957880949","data":{"timestamp":" 946957880949"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957883498","data":{"timestamp":" 946957883497"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957883636","data":{"timestamp":" 946957883636"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957892052","data":{"timestamp":" 946957892051"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957898746","data":{"timestamp":" 946957898746"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957904884","data":{"timestamp":" 946957904883"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 67f58731-96bb-4699-aee6-0d40345823f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957914940","data":{"timestamp":" 946957914940"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957915824","data":{"timestamp":" 946957915824"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957916466","data":{"timestamp":" 946957916466"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957916679","data":{"timestamp":" 946957916679"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957917362","data":{"timestamp":" 946957917362"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957917696","data":{"timestamp":" 946957917696"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957918190","data":{"timestamp":" 946957918190"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957921221","data":{"timestamp":" 946957921221"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957921555","data":{"timestamp":" 946957921555"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957922178","data":{"timestamp":" 946957922178"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957923395","data":{"timestamp":" 946957923395"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAPENDANA"," userResponse":" TUNAPENDANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957924176","data":{"timestamp":" 946957924176"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957926978","data":{"timestamp":" 946957926978"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITUMWA"," userResponse":" TUKITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957927953","data":{"timestamp":" 946957927953"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957928748","data":{"timestamp":" 946957928748"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957931737","data":{"timestamp":" 946957931736"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957932181","data":{"timestamp":" 946957932181"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957933025","data":{"timestamp":" 946957933025"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITUMWA"," userResponse":" NILITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957933650","data":{"timestamp":" 946957933650"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957933808","data":{"timestamp":" 946957933808"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957934296","data":{"timestamp":" 946957934296"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957934702","data":{"timestamp":" 946957934702"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957936352","data":{"timestamp":" 946957936352"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKANUNUE"," userResponse":" NIKANUNUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957937146","data":{"timestamp":" 946957937145"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957937674","data":{"timestamp":" 946957937673"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957938403","data":{"timestamp":" 946957938403"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957941192","data":{"timestamp":" 946957941192"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIENDA"," userResponse":" NILIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957941441","data":{"timestamp":" 946957941441"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957941980","data":{"timestamp":" 946957941979"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilienda na Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957944941","data":{"timestamp":" 946957944941"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIWA"," userResponse":" TUKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957945888","data":{"timestamp":" 946957945888"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957947020","data":{"timestamp":" 946957947019"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIWAONA"," userResponse":" TULIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957947644","data":{"timestamp":" 946957947643"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957948523","data":{"timestamp":" 946957948522"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZETU"," userResponse":" WENZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957949770","data":{"timestamp":" 946957949770"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957950296","data":{"timestamp":" 946957950296"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957950471","data":{"timestamp":" 946957950470"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957951012","data":{"timestamp":" 946957951011"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani tuliwaona watoto wenzetu wakicheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957953818","data":{"timestamp":" 946957953817"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957955194","data":{"timestamp":" 946957955193"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITAMANI"," userResponse":" NILITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957955834","data":{"timestamp":" 946957955834"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957956476","data":{"timestamp":" 946957956476"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957957068","data":{"timestamp":" 946957957067"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957957248","data":{"timestamp":" 946957957248"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nilitamani sana kucheza mpira huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957960258","data":{"timestamp":" 946957960257"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISEMA"," userResponse":" NILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957961067","data":{"timestamp":" 946957961065"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957964508","data":{"timestamp":" 946957964507"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpira!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957968056","data":{"timestamp":" 946957968056"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957968596","data":{"timestamp":" 946957968596"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957969850","data":{"timestamp":" 946957969850"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957970623","data":{"timestamp":" 946957970622"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUWAOMBE"," userResponse":" TUWAOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957971245","data":{"timestamp":" 946957971245"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957971656","data":{"timestamp":" 946957971656"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957972609","data":{"timestamp":" 946957972609"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957975111","data":{"timestamp":" 946957975111"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957975776","data":{"timestamp":" 946957975776"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957976413","data":{"timestamp":" 946957976413"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957976631","data":{"timestamp":" 946957976630"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957977337","data":{"timestamp":" 946957977337"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi hupenda mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957980333","data":{"timestamp":" 946957980333"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957981371","data":{"timestamp":" 946957981370"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALINIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957982501","data":{"timestamp":" 946957982501"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957982994","data":{"timestamp":" 946957982994"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957983858","data":{"timestamp":" 946957983858"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957984629","data":{"timestamp":" 946957984628"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957985129","data":{"timestamp":" 946957985129"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TURUDI"," userResponse":" TURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957985763","data":{"timestamp":" 946957985762"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chuma alinijibu Twende kwanza dukani halafu turudi kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957988889","data":{"timestamp":" 946957988889"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957989754","data":{"timestamp":" 946957989754"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957990244","data":{"timestamp":" 946957990243"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957991394","data":{"timestamp":" 946957991393"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUCHEZE"," userResponse":" TUCHEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957991970","data":{"timestamp":" 946957991970"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957992468","data":{"timestamp":" 946957992468"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini nilimwambia Chuma Tucheze kwanza wewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957995192","data":{"timestamp":" 946957995192"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIENDA"," userResponse":" TUKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957996006","data":{"timestamp":" 946957996006"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957996745","data":{"timestamp":" 946957996744"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957998071","data":{"timestamp":" 946957998071"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukienda nyumbani nyanya hataturuhusu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATATURUHUSU"," userResponse":" HATATURUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958001906","data":{"timestamp":" 946958001906"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUBALIWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUBALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958002118","data":{"timestamp":" 946958002118"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958002972","data":{"timestamp":" 946958002972"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZETU"," userResponse":" WENZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958004175","data":{"timestamp":" 946958004175"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUKACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958004755","data":{"timestamp":" 946958004755"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikubaliwa na wenzetu tukacheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958007893","data":{"timestamp":" 946958007893"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa golikipa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958008922","data":{"timestamp":" 946958008922"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa golikipa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLIKIPA"," userResponse":" GOLIKIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958013234","data":{"timestamp":" 946958013234"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJITAHIDI"," userResponse":" NILIJITAHIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958014032","data":{"timestamp":" 946958014032"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUDAKA"," userResponse":" KUDAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958014650","data":{"timestamp":" 946958014648"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijitahidi kudaka mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958017425","data":{"timestamp":" 946958017425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZANGU"," userResponse":" WENZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958018390","data":{"timestamp":" 946958018388"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958018998","data":{"timestamp":" 946958018998"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUNGA"," userResponse":" KUFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958019477","data":{"timestamp":" 946958019476"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958020190","data":{"timestamp":" 946958020189"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958020659","data":{"timestamp":" 946958020659"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzangu hawakuweza kufunga goli hata moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958023735","data":{"timestamp":" 946958023735"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958025110","data":{"timestamp":" 946958025106"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIOCHEZEA"," userResponse":" TULIOCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958026322","data":{"timestamp":" 946958026322"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958026550","data":{"timestamp":" 946958026549"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958027389","data":{"timestamp":" 946958027389"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGA"," userResponse":" MCHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958028543","data":{"timestamp":" 946958028542"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uwanja tuliochezea ulikuwa na mchanga mwingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGI"," userResponse":" MWINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958031280","data":{"timestamp":" 946958031280"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGOLI"," userResponse":" MAGOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958032059","data":{"timestamp":" 946958032058"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958032676","data":{"timestamp":" 946958032676"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958033276","data":{"timestamp":" 946958033276"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958034146","data":{"timestamp":" 946958034145"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magoli yake yalikuwa mawe makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958037042","data":{"timestamp":" 946958037042"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958037256","data":{"timestamp":" 946958037256"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958038110","data":{"timestamp":" 946958038110"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" MCHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958039154","data":{"timestamp":" 946958039154"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958039947","data":{"timestamp":" 946958039947"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958040730","data":{"timestamp":" 946958040730"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958041403","data":{"timestamp":" 946958041403"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUWA"," userResponse":" HATUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958041623","data":{"timestamp":" 946958041623"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958042176","data":{"timestamp":" 946958042176"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958045086","data":{"timestamp":" 946958045085"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" NILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958046072","data":{"timestamp":" 946958046072"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958048957","data":{"timestamp":" 946958048957"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958050255","data":{"timestamp":" 946958050255"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKEMEA"," userResponse":" ALINIKEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958051260","data":{"timestamp":" 946958051259"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ACHA"," userResponse":" ACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958051749","data":{"timestamp":" 946958051749"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958053846","data":{"timestamp":" 946958053845"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958054308","data":{"timestamp":" 946958054307"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958055032","data":{"timestamp":" 946958055031"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITAKA"," userResponse":" ULITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958055645","data":{"timestamp":" 946958055645"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUCHEZE"," userResponse":" TUCHEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958056202","data":{"timestamp":" 946958056202"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958056360","data":{"timestamp":" 946958056360"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958056755","data":{"timestamp":" 946958056754"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958057427","data":{"timestamp":" 946958057426"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni wewe ulitaka tucheze kabla ya kwenda dukani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958060293","data":{"timestamp":" 946958060292"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIRUDI"," userResponse":" TULIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958061269","data":{"timestamp":" 946958061269"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958061629","data":{"timestamp":" 946958061628"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958062468","data":{"timestamp":" 946958062467"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958063241","data":{"timestamp":" 946958063241"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958064168","data":{"timestamp":" 946958064168"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulirudi nyumbani bila chumvi wala mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958066874","data":{"timestamp":" 946958066873"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958068118","data":{"timestamp":" 946958068118"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMECHAFUKA"," userResponse":" TUMECHAFUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958068782","data":{"timestamp":" 946958068782"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958069226","data":{"timestamp":" 946958069226"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulikuwa tumechafuka kweli kweli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958072510","data":{"timestamp":" 946958072510"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMKUTA"," userResponse":" TULIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958072963","data":{"timestamp":" 946958072963"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958074589","data":{"timestamp":" 946958074588"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" AMEKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958075040","data":{"timestamp":" 946958075040"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulimkuta nyanya amekasirika mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958077426","data":{"timestamp":" 946958077425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" SWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958077560","data":{"timestamp":" 946958077560"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958078065","data":{"timestamp":" 946958078065"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958079111","data":{"timestamp":" 946958079110"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALITUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958079797","data":{"timestamp":" 946958079797"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958081076","data":{"timestamp":" 946958081075"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKUWA"," userResponse":" MMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958081542","data":{"timestamp":" 946958081542"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958081958","data":{"timestamp":" 946958081958"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958082113","data":{"timestamp":" 946958082112"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958083263","data":{"timestamp":" 946958083262"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Swali la kwanza alituuliza lilikuwa Mmekuwa wapi muda huu wote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958086926","data":{"timestamp":" 946958086925"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958087368","data":{"timestamp":" 946958087367"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958088457","data":{"timestamp":" 946958088456"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOTEZA"," userResponse":" TULIPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958089152","data":{"timestamp":" 946958089151"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958090652","data":{"timestamp":" 946958090651"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958092489","data":{"timestamp":" 946958092488"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASAMEHE"," userResponse":" NAWASAMEHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958092761","data":{"timestamp":" 946958092760"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958094043","data":{"timestamp":" 946958094042"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958094903","data":{"timestamp":" 946958094903"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIRUDIE"," userResponse":" MSIRUDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958095452","data":{"timestamp":" 946958095452"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958096503","data":{"timestamp":" 946958096502"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958096936","data":{"timestamp":" 946958096935"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958097512","data":{"timestamp":" 946958097511"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipogundua kuwa tulipoteza hela alisema Nawasamehe leo lakini msirudie tena kucheza bila ruhusa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUHUSA"," userResponse":" RUHUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958100609","data":{"timestamp":" 946958100607"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958101364","data":{"timestamp":" 946958101363"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958102304","data":{"timestamp":" 946958102303"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALISHA"," userResponse":" KUWALISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958102757","data":{"timestamp":" 946958102756"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958102946","data":{"timestamp":" 946958102946"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958103388","data":{"timestamp":" 946958103388"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulienda haraka kuwalisha kuku na bata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958106641","data":{"timestamp":" 946958106641"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958107731","data":{"timestamp":" 946958107729"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIOGA"," userResponse":" TULIOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958107931","data":{"timestamp":" 946958107931"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958108333","data":{"timestamp":" 946958108333"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958109419","data":{"timestamp":" 946958109419"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAFI"," userResponse":" WASAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958112257","data":{"timestamp":" 946958112254"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958112368","data":{"timestamp":" 946958112368"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAFI"," userResponse":" WASAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958119882","data":{"timestamp":" 946958119882"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958129031","data":{"timestamp":" 946958129031"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" b1d5cefb-d9c6-49f0-bfdd-64991d64d701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958138916","data":{"timestamp":" 946958138916"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958139299","data":{"timestamp":" 946958139299"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958139797","data":{"timestamp":" 946958139797"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958140150","data":{"timestamp":" 946958140149"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958140569","data":{"timestamp":" 946958140569"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958141055","data":{"timestamp":" 946958141054"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958141291","data":{"timestamp":" 946958141289"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958144498","data":{"timestamp":" 946958144498"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958144533","data":{"timestamp":" 946958144533"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958145268","data":{"timestamp":" 946958145268"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958145673","data":{"timestamp":" 946958145672"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958145978","data":{"timestamp":" 946958145978"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958146190","data":{"timestamp":" 946958146189"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958146395","data":{"timestamp":" 946958146395"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958146716","data":{"timestamp":" 946958146714"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958146947","data":{"timestamp":" 946958146946"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958150106","data":{"timestamp":" 946958150106"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958150513","data":{"timestamp":" 946958150513"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958153135","data":{"timestamp":" 946958153134"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958153344","data":{"timestamp":" 946958153344"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958153555","data":{"timestamp":" 946958153554"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958157112","data":{"timestamp":" 946958157112"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958160836","data":{"timestamp":" 946958160836"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958161859","data":{"timestamp":" 946958161859"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958164368","data":{"timestamp":" 946958164367"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958164515","data":{"timestamp":" 946958164515"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958171883","data":{"timestamp":" 946958171883"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958181808","data":{"timestamp":" 946958181808"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958187956","data":{"timestamp":" 946958187956"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958200470","data":{"timestamp":" 946958200470"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958209304","data":{"timestamp":" 946958209304"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958215898","data":{"timestamp":" 946958215898"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958221682","data":{"timestamp":" 946958221682"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958228657","data":{"timestamp":" 946958228657"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958297670","data":{"timestamp":" 946958297669"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 7ec40e26-9b02-43fa-abd1-55aeb5f1188e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958297765","data":{"timestamp":" 946958297765"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 3e25d96d-a22b-4767-a48f-645787f81c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIREFU"," userResponse":" VIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958304593","data":{"timestamp":" 946958304593"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 3e25d96d-a22b-4767-a48f-645787f81c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958311570","data":{"timestamp":" 946958311569"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 3e25d96d-a22b-4767-a48f-645787f81c4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_49"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miguuni alivaa viatu vya rangi ya machungwa vya visigino virefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958322122","data":{"timestamp":" 946958322122"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUKA"," userResponse":" RUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958327447","data":{"timestamp":" 946958327447"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958330961","data":{"timestamp":" 946958330961"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAMANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAMANI"," userResponse":" RAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958335570","data":{"timestamp":" 946958335570"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAMANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAMANI"," userResponse":" RAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958337153","data":{"timestamp":" 946958337153"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" REDIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REDIO"," userResponse":" REDIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958342895","data":{"timestamp":" 946958342895"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" REDIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REDIO"," userResponse":" REDIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958344458","data":{"timestamp":" 946958344458"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RANGI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958347216","data":{"timestamp":" 946958347216"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RANGI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" START_RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958348514","data":{"timestamp":" 946958348514"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RANGI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958350076","data":{"timestamp":" 946958350076"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAFIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958355237","data":{"timestamp":" 946958355237"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAFIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958356786","data":{"timestamp":" 946958356785"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" RAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958359783","data":{"timestamp":" 946958359783"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" RAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958361364","data":{"timestamp":" 946958361364"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RINDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958364964","data":{"timestamp":" 946958364963"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RINDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958366553","data":{"timestamp":" 946958366553"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RADHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADHI"," userResponse":" RADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958369217","data":{"timestamp":" 946958369217"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RADHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADHI"," userResponse":" RADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958370800","data":{"timestamp":" 946958370799"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958374049","data":{"timestamp":" 946958374049"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958376068","data":{"timestamp":" 946958376067"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958376194","data":{"timestamp":" 946958376194"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958382954","data":{"timestamp":" 946958382954"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958400031","data":{"timestamp":" 946958400031"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6950c207-f607-40be-bb05-c91454a86ea3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958424165","data":{"timestamp":" 946958424165"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 96ccbdf2-f288-4d9c-a26c-d3d8fde05fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958440477","data":{"timestamp":" 946958440477"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 96ccbdf2-f288-4d9c-a26c-d3d8fde05fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958447276","data":{"timestamp":" 946958447274"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 96ccbdf2-f288-4d9c-a26c-d3d8fde05fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958457083","data":{"timestamp":" 946958457082"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 96ccbdf2-f288-4d9c-a26c-d3d8fde05fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958512353","data":{"timestamp":" 946958512353"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6578f2fc-bb92-4a86-97f8-088c7e7ebcfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958536579","data":{"timestamp":" 946958536579"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6578f2fc-bb92-4a86-97f8-088c7e7ebcfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958536675","data":{"timestamp":" 946958536675"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6578f2fc-bb92-4a86-97f8-088c7e7ebcfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958543753","data":{"timestamp":" 946958543701"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6578f2fc-bb92-4a86-97f8-088c7e7ebcfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958556909","data":{"timestamp":" 946958556909"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6578f2fc-bb92-4a86-97f8-088c7e7ebcfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958565899","data":{"timestamp":" 946958565898"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 6578f2fc-bb92-4a86-97f8-088c7e7ebcfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022695503","data":{"timestamp":" 947022695503"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022695877","data":{"timestamp":" 947022695877"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022696361","data":{"timestamp":" 947022696360"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022696704","data":{"timestamp":" 947022696704"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022697110","data":{"timestamp":" 947022697110"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022697587","data":{"timestamp":" 947022697587"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022697812","data":{"timestamp":" 947022697812"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022701051","data":{"timestamp":" 947022701051"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022701084","data":{"timestamp":" 947022701084"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022701798","data":{"timestamp":" 947022701798"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022702192","data":{"timestamp":" 947022702192"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022702486","data":{"timestamp":" 947022702486"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022702691","data":{"timestamp":" 947022702691"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022702883","data":{"timestamp":" 947022702883"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022703197","data":{"timestamp":" 947022703197"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022703424","data":{"timestamp":" 947022703423"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022706630","data":{"timestamp":" 947022706630"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022707032","data":{"timestamp":" 947022707032"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022709650","data":{"timestamp":" 947022709650"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022709856","data":{"timestamp":" 947022709856"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022710059","data":{"timestamp":" 947022710059"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022713537","data":{"timestamp":" 947022713537"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022717317","data":{"timestamp":" 947022717317"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022718342","data":{"timestamp":" 947022718342"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022720658","data":{"timestamp":" 947022720658"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022720845","data":{"timestamp":" 947022720845"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022795859","data":{"timestamp":" 947022795858"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" 8a9df732-2622-4a24-a01e-c321ac421558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022797144","data":{"timestamp":" 947022797144"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" c750cb24-3d3c-4e34-9741-ccb0a44e1ca2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022816872","data":{"timestamp":" 947022816871"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000104_060152"," gameId":" c750cb24-3d3c-4e34-9741-ccb0a44e1ca2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_50"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}